<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>blazer &#8211; Shopie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product-category/blazer/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie</link>
	<description>Best shopping website</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/brand.png</url>
	<title>blazer &#8211; Shopie</title>
	<link>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>blazer</title>
		<link>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/blazer/</link>
					<comments>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/blazer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rahil]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/?post_type=product#038;p=84</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A blazer is a versatile and timeless piece of clothing that serves both functional and aesthetic purposes. It is typically made from materials such as leather, denim, wool, polyester, or synthetic blends, depending on its style and intended use. Black jackets are popular for their neutral color, which pairs well with a wide range of outfits and occasions.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="flex-shrink-0 flex flex-col relative items-end">
<div class="pt-0">
<div class="gizmo-bot-avatar flex h-8 w-8 items-center justify-center overflow-hidden rounded-full">
<div class="relative p-1 rounded-sm flex items-center justify-center bg-token-main-surface-primary text-token-text-primary h-8 w-8">
<p>this <strong> blazer</strong> is a versatile and timeless piece of clothing that combines comfort with effortless style. Typically made from soft and breathable materials like cotton or a cotton-blend, it’s designed to provide all-day comfort while being lightweight and easy to wear. The classic T-shirt comes in various styles, including crewneck, V-neck, and oversized fits, making it suitable for a wide range of preferences and occasions. Whether plain, patterned, or featuring bold graphics, a T-shirt is a staple in every wardrobe. It pairs seamlessly with jeans, shorts, or even skirts, making it perfect for casual outings, lounging at home, or layering under jackets. The T-shirt’s simplicity and adaptability ensure it remains a go-to choice for fashion and practicality alike.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/blazer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>printed blazer</title>
		<link>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/printed-blazer/</link>
					<comments>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/printed-blazer/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[rahil]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/?post_type=product#038;p=83</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A printed blazeris a versatile and timeless piece of clothing that serves both functional and aesthetic purposes. It is typically made from materials such as leather, denim, wool, polyester, or synthetic blends, depending on its style and intended use. Black jackets are popular for their neutral color, which pairs well with a wide range of outfits and occasions.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="flex-shrink-0 flex flex-col relative items-end">
<div class="pt-0">
<div class="gizmo-bot-avatar flex h-8 w-8 items-center justify-center overflow-hidden rounded-full">
<div class="relative p-1 rounded-sm flex items-center justify-center bg-token-main-surface-primary text-token-text-primary h-8 w-8">
<p>this <strong>printed blazer</strong> is a versatile and timeless piece of clothing that combines comfort with effortless style. Typically made from soft and breathable materials like cotton or a cotton-blend, it’s designed to provide all-day comfort while being lightweight and easy to wear. The classic T-shirt comes in various styles, including crewneck, V-neck, and oversized fits, making it suitable for a wide range of preferences and occasions. Whether plain, patterned, or featuring bold graphics, a T-shirt is a staple in every wardrobe. It pairs seamlessly with jeans, shorts, or even skirts, making it perfect for casual outings, lounging at home, or layering under jackets. The T-shirt’s simplicity and adaptability ensure it remains a go-to choice for fashion and practicality alike.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://rahil-313.github.io/shopie/product/printed-blazer/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
